Rare Pamphlet Collection 6034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 39, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Representation for labor, 1919; Publication (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Notes: Address before the National conference of state manufacturers' associations, St. Louis, Missouri, and The representation plan referred to therin .. 1919.
- Box: 39, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Profits and Wages: Employers Incomes and Workers Earnings, 1932; Publication (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Author: Anna Rochester
- Box: 39, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Your dollar under Roosevelt, 1933; Publication (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Box: 39, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Colorado industrial plan, 1916; Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Author: John D. Rockefeller
  - Item 2: The personal relation in industry, 1917; Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Brotherhood of men and nations, 1918; Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Notes: Address delivered before the Civic and Commercial Club at Denver, Colorado, June 13, 1918
  - Item 4: Representation in industry, 1918; Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Christian church: what of its future?, 1945; Publication (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Box: 39, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Women's Center Reid lectureship, 1978; Publication (Box 39, Folder 6)
    Author: Helen Rodriguez Trias
    Notes: November 10 and 11, 1976: two lectures
- Box: 39, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Strikes and the labour government, 1947; Publication (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Author: Douglas Rogers
- Box: 39, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Social General Strike, 1905; Publication (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Author: Arnold Roller
- Box: 39, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Reconversion-idle talk means idle men, 1944; Publication (Box 39, Folder 9)
    Notes: Address by George Romney before National Industrial Conference Board, September 21, 1944.
- Box: 39, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Code of fair competition for the dress manufacturing industry, Publication (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Why social security?, Publication (Box 39, Folder 10)
    Author: Mary Ross
- Box: 39, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The roots of prejudice, 1951; Publication (Box 39, Folder 11)
    Author: Arnold Marshall Rose
- Box: 39, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Stop the strike, Publication (Box 39, Folder 12)
    Author: Frank H. Rose
  - Item 2: Wealth, work, and wages: British industrialism in the Twentieth century, 1909; Publication (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Box: 39, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Employment stabilization program, 1943; Publication (Box 39, Folder 13)
    Author: United States. War Manpower Commission
- Box: 39, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Workers in the Soviet union, 1942; Publication (Box 39, Folder 14)
    Author: Andrew Rothstein
- Box: 39, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Disegno di legge sulla emigrazione italiana: osservazioni e proposte, 1888; Publication (Box 39, Folder 15)
    Author: Giovanni Battista Scalabrini
    Language: Italian.
- Box: 39, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Was Marx wrong?: the economic theories of Karl Marx, tested in the light of modern industrial development, 1914; Publication (Box 39, Folder 16)
    Author: I. M. Rubinow
- Box: 39, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The corroding effects of suspicion, Publication (Box 39, Folder 17)
    Author: Bertrand Russell
- Box: 39, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The farmer-labor united front, Publication (Box 39, Folder 18)
    Author: Charles E. Ruthenberg
  - Item 2: The Workers (Communist) Party: what it stands for, why workers should join, 1926; Publication (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: From the third through the fourth convention of the Workers (Communist) party of America, 1926; Publication (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Box: 39, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Supreme Court and the minimum wage, 1923; Publication (Box 39, Folder 19)
    Author: John Augustine Ryan
  - Item 2: The Constitution and Catholic industrial teaching, 1937; Publication (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: The Christian doctrine of property, 1923; Publication (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Can unemployment be ended?, 1940; Publication (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: A catechism of the social question, 1921; Publication (Box 39, Folder 19)
    Author: John Augustine Ryan; R. A. McGowan
- Box: 39, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Walled in this tomb: questions left unanswered by the Lowell Committee in the Sacco-Vanzetti Case and their pertinence in understanding the conflicts sweeping the world at this hour., 1936; Publication (Box 39, Folder 20)
    Author: [Sacco-Vanzetti Trial]
  - Item 2: Financial report of the Sacco-Vanzetti defense committee, 1925; Publication (Box 39, Folder 20)
    Author: Sacco-Vanzetti Defense Committee
    Notes: From the date of organization, May 5, 1920, to July 31, 1925.
  - Item 3: Are they doomed? [Sacco-Vanzetti Case and the Grim Forces behind it; by Art Shields. Highway robbery and Murder.], Publication (Box 39, Folder 20)
    Author: Nicola Sacco; Art Shields
- Box: 39, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Saint Paul picketeer, 1922; Publication (Box 39, Folder 21)
    Notes: v.1:no.33 (1922:Jan.11)
- Box: 39, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: An open letter to President Wilson, 1920; Publication (Box 39, Folder 22)
    Author: Benjamin Joseph Salmon
- Box: 40, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The rights of labor and property: their fundamental importance in American society, 1887; Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Author: William Salter
- Box: 40, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Marquise, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Author: George Sand
- Box: 40, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor racketeering: evolution and solutions, 1958; Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Author: David J. Saposs
  - Item 2: Anti-labor activities in the United States, 1938; Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Structure of AFL unions, 1939; Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Author: David J. Saposs; Sol Davison
  - Item 4: Union responsibility and incorporation of labor unions, 1938; Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Box: 40, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: What goes on, 1944; Publication (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Author: Jay Johnson Morrow Scandrett
- Box: 40, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Stalin's fifth column on Broadway, 1940; Publication (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Author: Louis Schaffer
- Box: 40, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The challenge of workers' education, 1951; Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Author: Theodore Schapiro
- Box: 40, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Practical and scientific management, Publication (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Author: G. Schlesinger
- Box: 40, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Karl Marx and the Civil War, Publication (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Author: Herman Schleuter
  - Item 2: Abraham Lincoln and the working class, 1921; Publication (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Box: 40, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Socialism in America, 1951; Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Author: Emerson Peter Schmidt
- Box: 40, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Youth betrayed, 1937; Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
    Author: Morris Bartel Schnapper; Ilse Trauman
- Box: 40, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Pacific Coast maritime strike, 1937; Publication (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Author: William Schneiderman
- Box: 40, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The great lesson of war, 1916; Publication (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Author: Edwin Davies Schoonmaker
- Box: 40, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Are all radicals insane?, 1921; Publication (Box 40, Folder 13)
    Author: Theodore Schroeder
- Box: 40, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Puerto Rican neighbor, 1954; Publication (Box 40, Folder 14)
    Author: Roy Schuckman
- Box: 40, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Labor hi-lites, 1938; Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
    Author: Charles Schwartz; Bernard Seaman
- Box: 40, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Labor monopolies-or freedom, 1946; Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
    Author: John Watson Scoville
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining, 1944; Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Box: 40, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Seacroft: a workers educational community., 1935; Publication (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Box: 40, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Racism and Southern unions, 1956; Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Author: Benjamin D. Segal
- Box: 40, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Unions and democracy: a brief account of problems in Union Democracy in The American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, Publication (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Box: 40, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Norris-LaGuardia act and the courts, 1941; Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
    Author: Melvin James Segal
- Box: 40, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: A labor party for America?, 1936; Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
    Author: Joel Isaac Seidman
  - Item 2: Shall strikes be outlawed?, 1938; Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Sit-down, 1937; Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Sit-down', by Joel Seidman.: A G.M. stockholder, 1937; Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
    Author: Joel Isaac Seidman; Robert Morss
  - Item 5: Introduction to labor problems, 1936; Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Box: 40, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Mediation and arbitration of industrial disputes, 1922; Publication (Box 40, Folder 22)
    Author: Benjamin M. Selekman
  - Item 2: The Menorah journal, 1926; Publication (Box 40, Folder 22)
    Author: N.Y.) Menorah Association (New York
    Notes: v.12:no.2 (1926:Apr./May)
- Box: 41, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A public debate: Capitalism vs. Socialism., 1921; Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Author: Edwin Robert Anderson Seligman
- Box: 41, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Workers, Apostles to workers, 1949; Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Author: Robert Senser
- Box: 41, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Strikes, 1935; Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Author: Joseph J. Senturia
- Box: 41, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Sewing machine operator training for the needle trades, 1962; Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Box: 41, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Capitalizing intelligence; eight essays on adult education, 1937; Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Author: Warren Crocker Seyfert
- Box: 41, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Ziegler Frame-Up, 1926; Publication (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Author: Max Shachtman
  - Item 2: For a cost-plus wage, 1943; Publication (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Box: 41, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The unprotected child and the law, 1923; Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Author: Bernard Shaw
  - Item 2: Socialism for millionaires, 1902; Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Box: 41, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Soviet war on religion, 1930; Publication (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Author: M. Sherwood
- Box: 41, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The National War Labor Board: its significance., 1945; Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Author: Joseph Shister
- Box: 41, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Shop paper manual: a handbook for comrades active in shop paper work, 1931; Publication (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Box: 41, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Education: an answer to poverty, 1965; Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
    Author: United States. Office of Economic Opportunity
    Notes: School programs which may be eligible for Federal aid.
- Box: 41, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: What do you know about British labor?, 1946; Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
    Author: David Shub; Robert J. Alexander; Norman Angell
- Box: 41, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: An appeal to reason, 1941; Publication (Box 41, Folder 13)
    Author: Frederick Shulman
- Box: 41, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Paris Commune: a story in pictures; The Lessons of the Commune, 1934; Publication (Box 41, Folder 14)
    Author: William Siegel; Alexander Trachtenberg
- Box: 41, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The man under the machine, 1910; Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
    Author: A. M. Simons
  - Item 2: Wasting human life, Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Box: 41, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Desegregation! Labors stake in the fight for negro equality., 1955; Publication (Box 41, Folder 16)
    Author: Jean Simon
- Box: 41, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: A great need of this hour; the outlawing of strikes., 1939; Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
    Author: Rembert Gilman Smith
- Box: 41, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: EPIC answers: how to end poverty in California, 1934; Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
    Author: Upton Sinclair
  - Item 2: Terror in Russia? Two views, 1938; Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
    Author: Upton Sinclair; Eugene Lyons
  - Item 3: The profits of religion; an essay in economic interpretation, 1918; Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Letters to Judd; an American workingman, 1949; Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: We, people of America, and how we ended poverty; a true story of the future, 1935; Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: A captain of industry: being the story of a civilized man, 1906; Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: A letter to Mr. Vincent Astor from Mr. Upton Sinclair, 1913; Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Box: 41, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: What can be done about America's economic troubles?, 1939; Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: The associated press and labor, 1920; Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
    Notes: Being seven chapters from The brass check; a study of American Journalism
- Box: 42, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The railroad strikes of 1877, 1937; Publication (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Author: Philip A. Slaner
- Box: 42, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Slave labor in the Soviet world, 1951; Publication (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Box: 42, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade unions in a free society, 1947; Publication (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Author: Sumner H. Slichter
  - Item 2: Basic criteria used in wage negotiations, 1947; Publication (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Creeping inflation: a debate between Sumner H. Slichter and Dr. Heinz Luedicke., 1957; Publication (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Author: Sumner H. Slichter; Heinz Luedicke
  - Item 4: Technology and the great American experiment, 1957; Publication (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Social security after the war, 1943; Publication (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Notes: Address given at Radcliffe College, April 4, 1943, in the series of Winthrop Ames memorial lectures.
- Box: 42, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: You've got a right, 1938; Publication (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Author: Sasha Small
- Box: 42, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Organized labor in the Soviet Union, 1944; Publication (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Author: Edwin Seymour Smith
  - Item 2: The demand for regulation of labor unions, 1938; Publication (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Notes: Address by Edwin S. Smith, member National Labor Relations Board, before the International Juridical Association, Saturday, January 15, 1938, New York, N.Y.
- Box: 42, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Jungle law or human reason?: the North Atlantic Pact and what it means to you, 1949; Publication (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Author: Jessica Smith
- Box: 42, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Bill of Rights and our individual liberties, 1954; Publication (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Author: Thomas Venor Smith
- Box: 42, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Catholic labor school: common sense in action, 1941; Publication (Box 42, Folder 8)
    Author: William J. Smith
  - Item 2: What is the Catholic attitude?: on big industry, on corporatism, on Liberalism, on Communism, on Facism, on Democracy, on race and color, on the worker, on the poor, on the rich?, Publication (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Box: 42, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Daily life in Parliament, 1930; Publication (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Author: Henry Snell
- Box: 42, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Socialism v. capitalism, 1923; Publication (Box 42, Folder 10)
    Author: Philip Snowden
    Notes: Verbatim report of a speech by Philip Snowden, M.P., in the House of Commons, March 20, 1923.
- Box: 42, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Social action, 1947; Publication (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Box: 42, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A labor party for the United States, 1936; Publication (Box 42, Folder 12)
    Author: Social Economic Foundation (New York)
- Box: 42, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Socialist handbook, 1937; Publication (Box 42, Folder 13)
    Author: Roy E. Burt
- Box: 42, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Your unions, your future, 1928; Publication (Box 42, Folder 14)
    Author: Socialist Party (U.S.)
    Notes: An address to the trade unions of the United States: an appeal to consider some of the grave problems confronting the organized workers.
- Box: 42, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: An appeal to the membership of the Socialist Party, 1934; Publication (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Box: 42, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: By-laws Socialist Party of New York City, 1926; Publication (Box 42, Folder 16)
    Author: Socialist Party of New York
- Box: 42, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Unionism industrial and political: the Philadelphia street car strike and general strike, 1910; Publication (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Box: 42, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Unions face the Depression, 1938; Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Labor in politics, 1915; Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: A plan for America: official 1932 campaign handbook of the Socialist party, Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
    Author: Edward Levinson; Maynard C. Krueger
  - Item 4: Inflation; who wins and who loses?, 1934; Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
    Author: Maynard C. Krueger
  - Item 5: Revitalize the labor movement: union militancy, union democracy, and workers control, Publication (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Box: 42, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: New deal for Labour, 1951; Publication (Box 42, Folder 19)
    Author: Socialist Party (India)
  - Item 2: A way forward; political realignment in America, political declaration of the 1960 national convention., Publication (Box 42, Folder 19)
    Author: Socialist Party-Social Democratic Federation
- Box: 42, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Workers League July 12 Conference: A Socialist Strategy for Labor, 1987; Publication (Box 42, Folder 20)
    Author: Workers League (U.S.)
- Box: 42, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Why we are in prison: farewell speeches of the 18 SWP and 544-CIO Minneapolis prisoners, 1944; Publication (Box 42, Folder 21)
    Author: Socialist Workers Party
  - Item 2: Declaration of principles and constitution of the Socialist Workers Party, 1938; Publication (Box 42, Folder 21)
    Notes: Adopted at the Foundation Convention, Chicago, Dec. 31, 1937 - Jan. 1-2-3, 1938.
  - Item 3: The Farmer-Labor Party: a program, 1938; Publication (Box 42, Folder 21)
    Author: Vincent R. Dunne
    Notes: An open letter to Governor Benson from the Socialist Workers Party, Minnesota Section
- Box: 43, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Social security bill; its taxing provisions, its advisability in the light of foreign experience, its major economic aspects and specific defects., 1935; Publication (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Author: National Association of Manufacturers (U.S.)
- Box: 43, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Exhibit of better industrial relations, Publication (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Author: Society for Ethical Culture
- Box: 43, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: How they won: the strike of the Warsaw tramwaymen, 1932; Publication (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Author: I. Sokol
- Box: 43, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Albany "trial", 1920; Publication (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Author: Charles Solomon
  - Item 2: Detroit and the Party, 1934; Publication (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Box: 43, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Union-smashing in Sacramento, the truth about the criminal syncicalism trial, 1935; Publication (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Author: Herbert Solow; Samuel S. White; Travers Clements
- Box: 43, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Songs of life and labour, 1926; Publication (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Author: John Stewart
- Box: 43, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Socialism and the worker, 1890; Publication (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Author: Friedrich A. Sorge
- Box: 43, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Building a new world., 1936; Publication (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Author: V. Chemadanov; George Soule
- Box: 43, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Women in German industry, 1949; Publication (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Author: Sara Southall; Pauline M. Newman
- Box: 43, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The substance of socialism, 1909; Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
    Author: John Spargo
  - Item 2: The common sense of socialism; a series of letters addressed to Jonathan Edwards, of Pittsburg, 1911; Publication (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Box: 43, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The struggle of the marine workers, 1930; Publication (Box 43, Folder 11)
    Author: N. Sparks
- Box: 43, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: How Socialists would run industry, Publication (Box 43, Folder 12)
    Author: Malcolm Sparkes
- Box: 43, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: International planning of public works; a factor in the regularization of employment and economic relationships, 1932; Publication (Box 43, Folder 13)
    Author: Thomas Gardner Spates
- Box: 43, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Stalin on the new Soviet constitution., 1936; Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)
    Author: Joseph Stalin
  - Item 2: The Lenin heritage, 1934; Publication (Box 43, Folder 14)